way2gamez.com 2010-12-02

# Play Free Online Games - Play Over 1000 + Free Flash games including Racing games, Shooting Games, Cricket , Pool , Chess , Action games, And most exciting 3D Games.

Way2gamez is committed to providing an entertaining, and fun  service. Way2gamez.com is a property of Way2online interactive  . Way2gamez respects the privacy concerns of visitors to Way2gamez.com. Way2gamez does not target its website or services to under 13 year olds, but does take measures to help protect those that happen to be under 13. We take measures to help children protect their privacy while online. For example, we do not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in a particular activity.

Information we collect  
We may log IP addresses and/or drop cookies to prevent abuse of our website and/or to enhance services. For the under 13 year olds who choose to sign up for the "Way2gamez Players" (which is not required to access the Way2gamez.com website) Way2gamez collects their parents email addresses and their date of birth when they choose to directly provide it. The parent has the option to agree to the collection and use of their child's information by the operator without consenting to the disclosure of that information to third parties.

How we use the information  
We have an internal notification system to communicate with under 13 players and do not send them emails. We do not retain any personal information beyond the time it is needed. We may use information to ensure that users are compliance with our terms. Over 13's may authorize and receive email notifications related to Way2gamez services. Way2gamez   may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with Way2gamez's property, visitors, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. 

We may sometimes use non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site, to personalize our visitors' experience or to offer products, programs, and services. We may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer products, programs, or services.

Collection of Information and Third-Party Sites and Sponsors  
We do not disclose personally identifiable information of under 13's to third parties. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies and Way2gamez   may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Third parties and or Way2gamez may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served. We may also share the anonymous information that we collect from you with our business partners or clients so that they may improve their services. We may use anonymous information that we collect from you to improve our services.

Information that is reasonably necessary  
Way2gamez does not require under 13's to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity as a condition of participation.

Security  
We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
This Privacy Policy is part of the Way2gamez main Terms and Conditions which you agree to by accessing the Way2gamez.com webstie and/or services. You agree that Way2gamez   may change this Privacy Policy and the main Way2gamez Terms and Conditions at any time.

We also reserve the right to comply with any order or otherwise cooperate with law enforcement officials regarding the identification of any user alleged to be using a Way2gamez   website or service in violation of the law.
